quizly.io 2016-06-23

# Privacy Policy | Quizly

### Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected byQUIZLY and how it is used.

Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  
QUIZLY does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [info@quizly.io](mailto:info@quizly.io)
